omsguru.com 2017-12-31

# Privacy Policy | OMS Guru

**Privacy Policy for OMSGuru**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by filling up the form.

At OMSGuru, we recognize that your privacy and the protection of your personal information is important, and, therefore have adapted this privacy. This privacy policy describes our privacy practices and how we treat the personal information that we collect from you when you use our products and services, including any personal information we collected from you when you created your account. The OMSGuru privacy policy applies to all of the products, services, and websites offered by OMSGuru or our related, affiliated and/or subsidiary companies (collectively, the “Products and Services”).

**What Personal Information We Collect**

OMSGuru collects personally identifiable information when you register on our site. The information collected may include, but is not limited to the following: email, name, phone, IP address, browser information, and address. Any comments or questions you submit may be recorded as well. Collection of information takes place at various times while navigating OMSGuru’s site and using its software, Products and Services. When entering OMSGuru’s site, information may be collected about previous sites the person has viewed. If questions or comments have been submitted via email or a forum on our website, personal information is collected as well.

**How We Use The Information Collected**

The goal of collecting customer and visitor information is to create an efficient and friendlier user experience while working with OMSGuru. Personal information submitted at the time of registration may be used by OMSGuru for the marketing and promotion of OMSGuru products that we feel may be of interest to you. We may contact you by email or phone for understanding your needs or requirements. This helps us build the product that aides you in the long term.

You may “opt out” of these marketing activities during the registration process, by updating your account settings or via postal mail. We may use demographic and/or profile data to tailor your experience on our sites, show you content that we think you may be interested in, and display content according to your preferences. Furthermore, we shall have the right to retain records of all data pertaining to use of the website including, but not limited to, usage, activity logs, and click-throughs. We may disclose such data to third parties provided it is grouped with other user data and is presented in an aggregate form. We may also disclose, on an anonymous basis, statements made by our customers.

**To Whom We Disclose Personal Information**

We take your privacy very seriously. None of the information that is collected by OMSGuru is rented or sold to any third parties for any purpose. Limited information may be shared with a third party that has partnered with OMSGuru if that information is protected under a confidentiality obligation with that third party and is used only as a part of providing the OMSGuru service to the customer. We reserve the right to disclose information when required by law.

**Other Information**

By submitting personal information to us or using our site, you agree that we may collect and use such personal information in accordance with our privacy policy or as permitted by law. If you do not agree with these terms, do not provide any personal information to us. If you refuse or withdraw consent, or do not provide us with any necessary personal information, we may not be able to provide you with products or service.

**Removal from our Database**

To request removal from the database, please submit a support request and we will be happy to remove your information promptly for a small fee. If you request that we modify or remove all of your personal information, we will promptly do so, to the extent possible. Once your personal information has been removed you will not be able to use our products or services unless you re-register. You may request details of personal information about you that we hold under the Data Protection Act 1998. If you would like a copy of the information held about you please send an email requesting this information to info@omsguru.com.

**Cookies**

When you use OMSGuru Products and Services, we send to your computer one or more cookies (i.e. a small file containing a string of characters) that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our Products and Services by storing user preferences and tracking. We may also use cookies to keep track of your session, shopping cart, and advertising delivery. We may use an outside ad company to display ads on our sites. These ads may also contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our websites, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company and we do not have access to this information. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Please note, however, some features of the Products and Services may not function properly, if at all, if your cookies are disabled.

We may use standard Internet technology, such as web beacons and other similar technologies, to track your use on our sites and software. We also may include web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. The information we obtain in this manner enables us to customize the services we offer our visitors/customers to deliver targeted advertisements and to measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, programming or other activities.

We may allow third parties, including our authorized service providers, advertising companies, and ad networks, to display advertisements on our sites and/or Products and Services. We and these companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with these advertisements and connect to our sites and/or Products and Services. Our sites do not provide any personal information to these third parties. This information allows us and these companies to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness.

**Links to other websites**  
From time to time this web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we, OMSGuru, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the terms of use and privacy statements of each and every web site they visit. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by OMSGuru

**IP Address**

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site and gather broad demographic information for aggregated used. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Security**

This web site has security measures in place designed to protect against loss, misuse and/or alteration of the information that you provide. Furthermore, we have taken reasonable precautions to prevent any unauthorized access to the contents of this web server.

**Changing of Personal Information**

You may edit your personal information at any time by clicking on the “My Account” tab when you are signed in to OMSGuru. All information may be changed including: address, email, phone and more. The new information will be updated in our system and used in the collection of information when visiting OMSGuru.

**Merger or Acquisition**

In the event that OMSGuru merges or is acquired by another company, all current information OMSGuru has will be shared with the other company. OMSGuru will do its best to inform you of the transaction. This Privacy Policy inures to the benefit of our successors and assigns.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there. This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

**Amendments**

We may amend this policy at any time. If we are going to use personally identifiable information collected through our sites in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email and/or by posting a notice on our site for thirty (30) days prior to such use. This Privacy Policy may not be amended by you except in a writing that specifically refers to this Privacy Policy and is physically signed by both parties.

**Consent**  
By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms of use.

**Questions, Comments, Concerns**

All questions, comments and concerns can be submitted by emailing info@omsguru.com. You will receive an answer as soon as possible.
